I was a ghost, I was alone
-- 我像個幽靈，我孤身一人
어두워진 앞길 속에 (ah)
-- 前方道路昏暗（啊）
Given the throne, I didn't know how to believe
-- 人面給我皇冠，我不知道該如何相信
I was the queen that I'm meant to be (oh)
-- 我就是我命中注定的女王（哦）
I lived two lives, tried to play both sides
-- 我過着双重生活，試圖兩邊都討好。
But I couldn't find my own place (oh, oh)
-- 但我找不到屬於自己的地方（哦，哦）
Called a problem child,'cause I got too wild
-- 我被叫做問題兒童，因为我太放蕩不羈了。
But now that's how I'm gettin' paid, 끝없이 on stage
-- 但現在這就是我獲得一切的方式，舞台上的我
I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin'
-- 我不再躲藏，現在我要閃耀光芒
Like I'm born to be
-- 仿佛我生来就是如此
We dreamin' hard, we came so far
-- 我們努力追夢，一路走來。
Now I believe
-- 現在我相信
We're goin' up, up, up, it's our moment
-- 我们要一路高歌猛進，這是屬於我們的時刻。
You know together we're glowin'
-- 你知道我們在一起光芒四射
Gonna be, gonna be golden
-- 將會，將會是黄金般的
Oh, up, up, up with our voices
-- 哦，讓我们高聲呐喊！
영원히 깨질 수 없는
-- 永不破碎
Gonna be, gonna be golden
-- 將會，將會是黄金般的
Oh, I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin'
-- 哦，我不再躲藏了，現在我要閃耀光芒！
Like I'm born to be
-- 仿佛我生来就是如此
Oh, our time, no fears, no lies
-- 哦，我們的时代，没有恐懼，没有谎言
That's who we're born to be
-- 我們生来就是如此。
Waited so long to break these walls down
-- 等待了這魔久才打破這些壁壘
To wake up and feel like me
-- 醒來後感覺像我
Put these patterns all in the past now
-- 现在就把這些模式都抛在腦後吧。
And finally live like the girl they all see
-- 最後，像她們都看到的那個女孩一樣生活。
No more hidin', I'll be shinin'
-- 不再躲藏，我要閃耀光芒
Like I'm born to be
-- 仿佛我生来就是如此
'Cause we are hunters, voices strong
-- 因為我們是獵人，聲音鏗鏘有力
And I know I believe
-- 我知道我相信
We're goin' up, up, up, it's our moment
-- 我们要一路高歌猛進，這是屬於我們的時刻。
You know together we're glowin'
-- 你知道我們在一起光芒四射
Gonna be, gonna be golden
-- 將會，將會是黄金般的
Oh, up, up, up with our voices
-- 哦，讓我们高聲呐喊！
영원히 깨질 수 없는
-- 永不破碎
Gonna be, gonna be golden
-- 將會，將會是黄金般的
Oh, I'm done hidin', now I'm shinin'
-- 哦，我不再躲藏了，现在我要閃耀光芒！
Like I'm born to be
-- 仿佛我生来就是如此
Oh, our time, no fears, no lies
-- 哦，我们的时代，没有恐懼，没有谎言
That's who we're born to be
-- 我们生来就是如此。
You know we're gonna be,
gonna be golden (oh)
-- 你知道我们將會，將會變得非常出色（哦）
We're gonna be, gonna be (oh)
-- 我们將會，將會（哦）
Born to be, born to be glowin' (oh)
-- 天生如此，天生閃耀（哦）
밝게 빛나는 우린
-- 我们光芒四射
You know that it's our time,
no fears, no lies (oh, oh)
-- 你知道這是屬於我们的时代，没有恐懼，没有谎言（哦，哦）
That's who we're born to be!
-- 這就是我們生来就该成為的樣子！